downloadsongs1.win 2017-06-06

# Privacy – DownloadSongs1.win

At DownloadSONGS1.win we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by DownloadSONGS1.win and how we use it.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, DownloadSONGS1.win makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

DownloadSONGS1.win uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * AdFly
  * PopAds
  * Popcash
  * Google
  * Revenuhits

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on DownloadSONGS1.win and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

DownloadSONGS1.win has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

#### Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. DownloadSONGS1.win’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

#### Children’s Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

DownloadSONGS1.win does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that DownloadSONGS1.win has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

#### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

 **Disclaimer** : downloadsongs1.win is in no way endorsed or affiliate with any Mp3 files downloading website for example, mp3skull.com, mp3chief.com, songspk.name, downloadming.tv, allmusic.com, beemp3s.org, mp3lio.com, djmaza.info, indiamp3.com, emp3world, mp3raid, hulkshare, red.fm, torrents, mp3bear.com, emusic.com, mp3mad.com, raaga.com, pagalworld, mr-jatt.com, raaghits.net, mp3hungama.com, abmp3.me, djpunjab, djraag or any other mp3 sharing or downloading website. We are just a Music Search Engine. We are just indexing all of these mp3 providers website and providing you a broad songs search like Google does for web. We have only categorized these music file providers website. We have nothing to do with any of these songs downloading websites. We are not providing any mp3 download links directly or indirectly form our servers or resources. If any of these mp3 sites are providing music downloads without the owners permission or copyright. And you are the legal owner of these mp3. So you can take any legal action against them but You can not take any action against us. It's users choice whether they make search or not and follow any external websites link. You can not compensate us for that.
